德州长子 第一季第八集
本字幕由深影字幕组原创翻译
翻译  Daisy   花泽kally
翻译  爱因斯秋   shy哥滔
校对  shy哥滔
压制  陌路
德州长子 前情提要
Previously on AMC's "The Son"...
骑马去加西亚牧场找人帮忙
Ride to the García Ranch and get some help.
- 这是什么 - 你骑过了渗油的地方
- What is it? - You rode through an oil seep.
皮特 你变了
Something's changed in you, Pete.
我们不能再这样生活了
We can't live like this.
你在城市里开心吗
Are you happy here in the city?
那你和孩子们应该留下来
Then you and the kids should stay.
我的丈夫没死
My husband didn't die.
我对每个人都这样撒谎 但我不想对你说谎
It's a lie I told everyone, but I don't want to lie to you.
今晚我会去你的帐篷
I'll come to your teepee tonight.
见鬼 看看它们
Damn. Look at 'em all.
我没想到会和你发生关系
I didn't mean for that to happen.
我不是为了这事来的
That's not why I came over.
没关系的
I didn't think that.
我得走了
I need to go.
别
No, hey.
留下
Stay.
皮特 我不应该在这儿
I have no business being here, Peter.
你是已婚的人
You're married.
我和萨莉结束了
Sally and I are over.
我们之间没有牵连了
There's nothing left between us.
之前你也说过类似的话
I've heard this kind of talk before.
我认真的 这次不同
I mean it. Th... This is different.
我发誓
I promise.
留下吧
Stay.
这儿吗 留在你家吗
Here? In your house?
我让佣人们休假了
I gave the help the day off.
我不想像以前一样偷偷摸摸的了
I'm not sneaking around like we used to.
过了那个年纪了
I'm just too old for it.
和我一起吃晚饭吧
Just have dinner with me.
- 让我解释 - 解释什么
- Let me explain. - Explain what?
都行 你想听什么我就说什么
Anything. Anything you need explained.
我给他讲了
So, I told him,
"伙计 如果你想让我给你服务
"Amigo, if you want me to put my finger there,
先得娶了我"
you'll need to put a ring on it first."
他怎么回答
What'd he say to that?
他脸马上红了 说要给我双倍的钱
He turned bright red and offered to pay me double.
干得好
Oh! Well done, my girl.
那你收下钱了吗
So, did you take the money?
你以为呢 跟牌加注
Oh, what do you think? Call and raise.
下午好 姑娘们
Good afternoon, my soiled doves.
"妈妈" 下午好
Afternoon, Mama.
有人想出门走走吗
Anybody feel like a bit of travel?
别再去什么联谊会了
Mm. No more Aggie parties.
大学里那帮小崽子
Them college boys wouldn't know gratuity
只知道掏鸟不知道掏钱
if it bit them on the pecker.
不 这回可都是达官贵人
No, this is a high-born affair...
撒迪厄斯·基尔伯恩筹办了一次甜蜜狩猎
One of Thaddeus Kilborne's Honey Hunts.
数不完的农场主和石油大亨
Wall-to-wall ranchers and oil men,
帕提罗·希金斯 查普曼父子和比尔·斯特林
Pattillo Higgins, the Chapmans, Bill Sterling.
听说伊莱·麦卡洛上校本人
And rumor has it that Colonel Eli McCullough, himself,
也会露面
is gonna put in an appearance.
太好了
Well, la-di-da.
基尔伯恩通知每个招待所了
Kilborne put the word out to all the boarding houses.
有人感兴趣吗
Anybody interested?
我去
I'll go.
莉娜去了 还有吗
Lena's in. Anybody else?
不 谢了
Oh, no, thank you.
上次我被螨虫咬了
Last time I got my ass bit by chiggers.
有人吗
Anybody?
积极点吧
Oh, come on, gals.
说不定讨个有钱的老公
You might catch yourself a rich husband.
或者男人染上莉娜的水泡
Or he might catch Lena's social blisters.
他要是这样算走运了
He'd be a lucky fella if that's all he gets.
米格尔 交给你了
There you go, Miguel. You know what to do.
谢谢
Thank you.
菲尼
Finn!
儿子 真高兴 你总算来了
Good to see ya, boy! Oh, glad you could make it.
不想错过 这儿设置齐全
Oh, wouldn't miss it. It's quite a setup here.
那确实
Well, it is that.
基尔伯恩的老爹是个炒房客
Kilborne's daddy was a property speculator.
他的钱说不定都是靠卖烂房给别人来的
Made all his money selling bad lots to settlers.
那些人什么毛病啊
What was wrong with them?
那些房子刚刚好就在
Well, it just happened it was smack in the middle
科曼切人的地界儿上
of Comanche territory.
看来历史的细节被人遗忘了
It looks like history's forgotten the details.
总是这样
Well, it always does.
这片地还不错 不是吗
It's a nice spread, though, isn't it?
可以吗
May I?
麦卡洛上校
Colonel McCullough?
请随意
Of course. Be my guest.
百发百中啊
That was a hell of a shot!
上校
Colonel?
那是我的弓
That's my bow.
是啊
Indeed it is.
- 吃了吗 - 没 饿坏了
- Have you eaten? - Nah, famished.
来得正好 正是吃午饭的时候
Good. You're just in time for lunch.
上校
Colonel!
撒迪厄斯·基尔伯恩法官
Ah, Judge Thaddeus Kilborne.
真感谢你筹办了这么个盛会
A laudable affair you've put together here.
别客气
My pleasure.
这位是你常提起的令郎 皮特是吗
Is this your boy I heard so much about? Pete?
我是另一个 菲尼亚斯
I'm the other one. Phineas.
很荣幸 法官大人
It's a pleasure, Your Honor.
叫我撒迪厄斯就好
Oh, call me Thaddeus.
我十分希望你能留下来
I do hope you plan to stick around
参加今晚的甜蜜狩猎
for the Honey Hunt tonight.
- 额... - 我们不会错过的
- Well... - Wouldn't miss it for the world.
他的弟弟结婚了
His brother's married, but this one here,
但这个是出了名的花花公子
he's a legendary cocksman.
父亲真是过奖了
Well, my daddy exaggerates my exploits.
好小子 有主见
Oh, attaboy. Admit to nothing.
- 上校 - 撒迪厄斯
- Colonel. - Thaddeus.
但愿有这个必要
I suppose that was necessary.
小心不出大错
Better safe than sorry.
我也不是讨厌圣安东尼奥来的这群酒鬼
Not that I don't love the drunk assholes of San Antone,
但是你把我叫来干嘛
but why did you call me here?
祸不单行
Misery loves company.
不 说真的 怎么了
No, really. Why'd you call?
我发现一处渗油点
I found an oil seep.
检测表明
Had it tested.
是低硫原油
Sweet crude.
那你有什么顾虑呢
So, what's the problem?
它在佩德罗·加西亚的地盘上
It's on Pedro García's land.
他知道么
Does he know?
我想最好还是别声张
Well, I thought it best to keep it under my hat.
好吧 有什么计划
All right, well, what's the plan?
按照麦金尼家族那样
Same thing the McKinneys did.
按照常人的做法
Same thing everybody does.
谢谢
Thank you.
但是佩德罗不是那些脏兮兮的文盲农民
Yeah, but Pedro's not some illiterate dirt farmer.
他会反抗 战胜我们
He'll contest it, and he'll win.
除非他死了
Not if he's gone.
我不明白你到底什么意思
I'm trying to figure out what you're suggesting here.
那是佩德罗的问题
Well, that's Pedro's problem.
我希望他能理智点
I'm hoping he'll be reasonable.
有人想侵占他的土地
About as reasonable as you'd be
你还想让他和你一样理智吗
if someone were trying to chisel you out of your land?
你觉得我们还有办法吗
Do you think we have a choice here?
米德基夫给的钱还能用多久
When does the rest of that money from Midkiff run out?
到圣诞节... 省着用的话
Christmas... if we're careful.
而且 我们还得等新钻井
In the meantime, we're still waiting for that new rig to arrive.
即便钻井到手了
And once it does show up,
多长时间才能钻出油呢
how long is it gonna take us to hit oil?
几个月 几年
Months? Years?
菲尼 你和我要打拼出一些成果...
We're building something here, Finn, you and me...
遗产
A legacy.
你懂的 对不对
You know that, right?
我们想要的未来...
The future we want...
我们为之努力的未来...
the future we're working toward...
如果我们现在不做到 就都没有了
it won't happen unless we make it happen.
至于加西亚的地... 势必要拿下
And that García land... It's a sure thing.
好吧
All right, then.
皮特怎么办
What do we do about Pete?
不让他知道
Keep him out of it.
- 他会很快发现的 - 不能那么快
- He'll find out soon enough. - Well, not that soon.
我让他去奥斯汀了
I sent him up to Austin.
怎么了
What?
他和萨莉大吵一场
He and Sally had a big fight.
他现在应该回牧场了
He'll be back at the ranch by now.
糟了
Shit.
我们可以跟他谈谈
We can talk to him.
你这么觉得吗
You think so?
我印象里
The last time I checked,
玛丽亚·加西亚可还是他们家族的人
Maria García was still a member of that family.
那都是很久以前的事了
Well, that all happened a long time ago.
你弟弟就是个放不下的人
Well, your brother doesn't let things go that easy.
别让他知道
Keep him in the dark.
萨莉怎么了
What happened with Sally?
她想留在大城市里 那里过得开心
She's gonna stay in the city, where she's happy.
那是她该待的地方
It's where she belongs.
这是你俩都想要的结果吗
And is that what you both want?
是啊
Yeah.
你打算自己在这儿住
So you're gonna stay here alone?
只要这里属于我们 我就一直住下去
I figure, so long as we can hang onto this place.
你的孩子怎么办
What about your kids?
来点红酒么
Want some wine?
我们所有的红酒杯都被击碎了
All our wine glasses got shot up,
我们只能用这个凑合一下
so we'll have to make do with these.
我不知道如果每天见不到孩子们我该怎么活
I don't know how I'll survive without seeing the kids every day.
说实话 他们还是最好住在城市里...
Truth is, they're better off in the city...
也更安全
and safer.
伊莱不是这样的
It's different with Eli.
法官大人
Your Honor?
能占用您一些时间吗
Might I trouble you for a moment?
当然可以 孩子
Well, sure thing, son.
您觉得这个小晚宴
Do you think this little soiree has been
是不是空前的成功
a resounding success, or what?
谢谢夸奖
I thank you for that.
看来你的篮子里有宝贝啊
So, you got any aces in that basket there?
那是 您可仔细瞧好了
Well, you'll have to have a look.
真不赖
Well, now.
这是上校给您的礼物
It's a gift from the Colonel.
这次他又想干什么
What does he need this time?
这个 法官大人...
Well, Your Honor...
您办公室里 有一些档案
there are a few records in your office
我们想修改一下
we would like to have altered.
继续说
I'm listening.
加西亚家的地
The García tract.
佩德罗已经十年没交税了
Pedro hasn't paid his taxes in 10 years now,
罚金也就越积越多
and the penalties have added up substantially.
按道理 这地应该拍卖的
In fact, it's probably time for a sheriff's sale.
老天
Hell.
真庆幸你不是我邻居
I'm sure glad you're not my neighbor.
这里头一共是多少
How much is in there?
五千元
5,000.
佩德罗·加西亚从没漏交过税
Pedro García has always paid his taxes on time.
那是自然
We know that.
他肯定有记录和收据
He'll have records and receipts,
但我估计你也知道
but I guess you know that, too.
没错 先生
We do, sir.
我们是不是太贪腐了
We are rotten, aren't we?
真是欲壑难填啊
I mean, how much does one man need?
我在这拥有的土地和特拉华州相当
I-I got a piece of land here the size of Delaware,
但当我看到钱的时候
but I see a pile of money,
仍然无法拒绝
I can't stop myself from picking it up.
我就当你同意了
I'll take that as a "yes."
这些先当作定金吧 算一半
Let's make this payment the first half,
事成之后再付另外的一半 怎么样
rest due upon completion of the task, hmm?
可以 先生
Yes, sir.
天哪
Boy.
谢谢你
Thank you.
那么
So...
你之前没开玩笑吧
were you serious before?
我什么都能问吗
I get to ask whatever I want?
当然
Sure.
你和别人有过吗
Have there been other women?
除我以外
Besides me?
我结婚以后就没有了
Not once I got married, no.
那结婚前呢
What about before?
我还是个孩子
I was a kid.
我知道 我记得
I know. I remember.
但你第一次肯定不是跟我
But I couldn't have been your first.
在我十四岁 还在墨西哥的时候
My father took us to a whorehouse
我爸带我们去了妓院
when I was 14 in Mexico.
你喜欢吗
Did you like it?
我去的时候才十四岁啊
I was a 14-year-old boy in a whorehouse.
你觉得我能怎样
What do you think?
然后就认识了你
And then I met you.
然后呢
And?
没有然后
No "and."
你是我女朋友 我心里只有你
You were my girlfriend. I was faithful.
但你结婚了
Until you got married.
对
Yeah.
然后我结婚了
Then I got married.
这桩婚事对你父亲为什么那么重要
Why did it mean so much to your father?
为什么得娶萨莉
Why Sally?
他在乎的是她们家的威望
He liked that her family was respectable.
我不太明白
I don't understand it.
我也不懂
Me neither.
你想让我帮你问他吗
You want me to ask him for you?
不
No.
那你呢
What about you?
好吧
Well...
你是我的第一次
you were my first.
但之后我去了纽约 然后
But then I moved to New York, and...
就遇上了别人
there were others.
真正的淑女可不会这样
Too big a number for a lady.
在我年轻的时候
When I was younger,
我老是在想... 为什么自己没怀孕
I always... wondered why I didn't get pregnant.
而我的朋友们却总是能怀上
I watched all of my friends dealing with it all the time.
然后
But...
我意识到可能我就是怀不上
then I just realized maybe I couldn't get pregnant.
我没法生育
Maybe I can't.
你在意吗
Does that bother you?
完全不会
Not at all.
你为什么不想结婚
Why don't you want to get married?
我想自己来挑
I want to choose.
你想要自由
You want freedom...
但你却有个奴隶
and yet you own a slave.
这倒挺有意思
I find that funny.
没人强迫你留在这
Nobody asked you to be here.
你如果想要自由
If you wanted to be free, you should have stayed
你就该待在白人的地盘
where the white people come from.
可能伊莱现在就在那
Eli is probably there right now.
我希望今晚 他能睡在一张羽绒床上
I hope he's sleeping in a big feather bed tonight,
还枕着两个枕头
two pillows under his head.
羽绒床是什么
What's a "feather bed"?
天堂
Heaven.
我不懂
I don't understand.
当然
No!
你当然不懂
Of course you don't.
因为你就是个恶心的野蛮人
'Cause you're just a disgusting savage.
动手啊 想打就打吧
Go on. You can hit me for saying that if you want.
我不介意 毕竟欺凌弱小的感觉确实不错
It's okay. I know it makes you feel strong.
你也就剩这么点本事了 对吧
It's the only power you have left, isn't it?
我们其实是一类人
You and me, we are not so different.
在我当奴隶的这段时间里
I've been a slave for a while now,
我明白了一些事情
and I've learned a few tricks.
当你的新郎跟你发生关系的时候
When your new husband is putting his baby in you,
或许能让你想起过去美好的时光
it might help you to think of a happy memory from your past.
或许是时候好好想想伊莱
Maybe that would be a good time for you to remember Eli.
你的老公怎么做的
So, what happened with your husband?
亨利抛弃了我 因为发现我无法生育
Henry left me... when I couldn't give him a baby.
不过没关系 他是个好男人
But it's okay. He wasn't a good man.
我不知所措
I was stuck.
你知道吗
You know that?
我们过去住在康州格林尼治村的出租房里
We were living in a tenement in Greenwich Village.
一层楼的住户共用一个卫生间
We shared a bathroom with the whole floor.
我把婚戒当了才买到车票回家
I had to pawn my wedding ring to get a ticket home.
你可以找我啊 我会帮你的
You could've contacted me. I would've helped you.
是吗
Really?
你会给我汇钱吗
You would have wired me money?
瞒着萨莉
Behind Sally's back?
玛丽亚 我肯定会帮你的
I would've done something to help you, Maria.
拜托 你得信我
Come on. You have to know that.
我还以为我们能成一对
I thought we were gonna get married.
可是你因为一面之缘的女人... 抛弃了我
And then you left me... for a woman you just met.
我也于心不忍 我每时每刻都在想你
It was awful for me, too. I missed you all the time.
我恨我父亲替我做的决定
I hated my father putting me in that position.
是啊
Yeah.
你一定很煎熬吧
I'm sure you suffered.
你有自己的生活
You had a life.
你可以随心所欲无所顾忌
You could do whatever you wanted.
可我不像你有得选
I don't have any of your choices.
我没有钱 没有本事 没办法独自维生
I have no money, no skills, no way to survive on my own.
你难道不懂吗
Do you not understand that?
没错
You're right.
我对你不公平
I haven't been fair to you.
我希望再来一次
I wish I could take that time back,
做些弥补
do it all different.
你不行
Well, you can't.
我可以的
No, I can't.
对不起
I'm sorry.
真对不起
你们是来打鹌鹑的吗
Are you here to shoot quail?!
不是
No! No!
你们是来打野鸭的吗
Are you here to hunt duck?
不是
No! No!
当然不是
God damn right, you're not.
我满怀荣幸 欢迎各位参加
It is with enormous pleasure that I welcome y'all
撒迪厄斯·基尔伯恩主办的第三届甜蜜狩猎
to Thaddeus Kilborne's Third Annual Honey Hunt!
每一位美女的篮子里
Now, each of these fine ladies
装着一瓶波本威士忌
has a basket with a bottle of bourbon...
- 好呀 - 一个核桃派
- Yeah! - A pecan pie...
- 没错 - 还有一条毯子
- Yeah! - And a blanket...
以免芒刺粘在裤子上
so you don't get burrs on your trousers.
我们让这群姑娘先跑一步
We'll let these ladies get a little head start,
然后再开始捕猎
and then we'll start huntin'!
没错 我们可不能刁难他们
That's right, we can't make it too difficult for them.
你跟撒迪厄斯说了吗
You speak to Thaddeus?
说了
Yeah.
顺利吗
How'd it go?
这辈子最没难度的会面
Easiest meeting of my life.
有迟疑吗
Second thoughts?
顺其自然吧
It is what it is.
- 既然这样... - 是的
- Well, given the situation... - Yeah.
- 我们还是分开吧 - 最好不过了
- We should split up. - Probably for the best.
你要去哪 到这来
Where you going? Come back here!
诶哟哟
Well, well!
算你走运
Lucky you.
你好
Hi.
要坐会儿吗
Wanna sit?
虽然很诱人
Uh, that's a lovely invitation,
但是你应该更喜欢
but I think you'd prefer one of the other gentlemen
等会儿过来的男人吧
who's about to come this way.
这就未必了
Oh, I don't know.
我看你就很帅啊
You look pretty handsome to me.
你的结婚戒指去哪了
And what happened to your wedding ring?
丢了吗
You lose track of it?
可惜了 我还没有遇上心仪的姑娘
Tragically, I have not yet met the right young lady.
或许应该有所改变
Maybe that's about to change.
我们在毯子上哪也不去
We're not stepping off this blanket
除非我让你忘记...
until I make you forget...
每一个...
every...
相处过的女人
woman you've ever been with.
小姐 你的志气值得赞扬
Your ambition does you credit, ma'am.
喜欢吗
You like this?
谁不喜欢香吻呢 很舒服
Who doesn't like kisses? They are very pleasant.
这样呢
How 'bout this?
这个嘛...
That is, uh...
你太热情了
That's very kind of you.
现在呢
Well... how 'bout this?
你放轻松
You just relax...
幻想我是另一个人
and pretend I'm someone else.
您是伊莱·麦卡洛上校吧
You are Colonel Eli McCullough, right?
正是在下
Guilty as charged.
我不会说科曼切语
I don't speak Comanche.
但至少你听出来了
But you knew enough to recognize it.
你们是那个部落的
Who are your people?
不是科曼切
Not Comanche.
但你应该认识
But I think you might know them.
这又是怎么回事 亲爱的
What's this about, honey?
想让我掏钱还有更简单的办法
There's easier ways to get money off me.
我不是来要钱的
I'm not here for money.
我是里本阿帕奇人
I'm Lipan Apache.
墨西哥来的
From Mexico.
维拉村落附近吗
Near Villa Unión?
你们一群人闯进了我们村子
You and your men came into my village.
除了我的父亲
You killed everyone you could find,
找得到的都杀光了
except my father.
有趣的是
You know what's funny,
我以为你已经忘记了
is I wasn't even sure you would remember.
我记得很清楚
I remember him well.
很就以前的事了
That was a long time ago.
当时的我还不是这样
I was a different man then.
你父亲和族人杀了我的妻儿
And your father and his people killed my wife and son.
为你妻儿报仇要杀掉村子里所有人吗
An entire village for your wife and son?!
这段纠葛早就化解了
That war's long over.
来坐吧
Come and sit down.
你不知道我们还有很多共同点
We have more in common than you think.
站住
Stop.
你叫什么名字
Tell me your name.
伊莱
Eli?!
天哪
Oh, God.
救命
Help.
救命啊
Help!
我中枪了
I've been shot!
抱不过来的
Can't hold them all.
被你干掉的人命数得过来吗
Can you even count all the lives you've ended?
怎么回事
What's happening here?
你是印第安神祗传来的神谕
Are you a message from The Great Spirit?
那个阿帕奇女孩
That Apache gal...
她就是指示
Pretty sure that was a message.
她想置我于死地
She just wanted me dead.
那就是给你的指示
That's a hell of a message.
骑马去
Get on the horse.
我还没准备好
I'm not ready.
你就是杀人机器啊 老头
You're a loaded gun, old man.
没了你的世界更美好
It's a better world without you in it.
别急
Easy there.
来吧 我们一起
Come on. We'll do it together.
听得见吗
Can you hear me?
别回头
Don't look back.
坚持住 爸爸
Hang on. Hang on, Daddy.
别回头
Don't look back.
爸爸撑住 我们带你去看医生
Hold on, Daddy. We're gonna get you to a doctor, okay?
爸爸撑住 有我在
Hang on, Daddy! I gotcha!
爸 别放弃 我们带你去看医生
Daddy?! Hold on. We're gonna get you to a doctor, okay?
告诉我们 怎么回事
Okay, but tell us, you gotta tell me what happened.
我没事
I'm fine.
谁干的 告诉我 是谁对你下的手
Well, who did this?! Tell me! Who did this to you?!
不知道 没看清是谁
I don't know. I didn't see the fella.
他中正你的胸膛 怎么会没看见呢
Well, he shot you in the chest! How did you miss seeing him?!
太黑了
It was dark!
好了 对不起
All right. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
别愣着
Don't just stand there!
快 找人帮忙 去开车
Come on! Go get some help! Get a truck started!
得救他出去
We gotta get him outta here!
很快就天亮了
It'll be light soon.
我得走了
I gotta go.
别走
No.
我会编个故事
Mm, I'll have to invent some story.
我要告诉家人
I'll have to tell them
我在朋友家过夜了
that I spent the night at a friend's house.
你是成熟的女性了
You're a grown woman.
我还是为人子女
I'm still their daughter.
去他的
Hell with that.
带上东西 来吧
Get your things. Come on.
什么
What?
你不希望别人对你指指点点
You don't want anyone telling you what to do anymore,
品头论足
how to live your life...
那 我们就走
so come on, let's go.
你开玩笑的
You're joking.
楼上的保险箱里还有点钱
We got some money in the safe upstairs.
我们去蒙大拿 我去给人打下手
We'll head up to Montana. I'll get work there as a hand.
- 我们现在就走吧 - 不
- Let's leave right now. - No.
- 不再回来 - 别这样
- Never come back. - Do... Don't.
你不能这么对我
You can't say that to me.
这样不公平
It's not fair.
我爱你
I love you.
我不要跟有妇之夫私奔 皮特
I'm not running off with a married man, Pete.
你打消这个念头吧
So put that out of your head.
好的
Okay.
那我们怎么办
So, what are we gonna do?
是谁
Who is it?
佩德罗·加西亚
Pedro García.
门没锁 进来吧
It's not locked. Come on in.
你好啊 兄弟
How are you, amigo?
要喝点东西吗
Can I get you something?
我可以煮一壶咖啡
I can make a pot of coffee.
不用了
No.
我一会儿就走
I won't stay long.
玛丽亚彻夜未归
Maria was out all night.
我觉得她在这
I believe she was here.
我结婚了 佩德罗
I'm a married man, Pedro.
你的种种猜测 我觉得你是误会了
Whatever you think is going on, I believe you're mistaken.
我的女儿...
My daughter...
她是寡妇
she's a widow.
她悲痛成疾
She's sick with grief
对于行为无法负责
and not responsible for her actions.
要是有人占了这个便宜
A man who takes advantage of this...
根本不算男人
is not a man at all.
我没有占你女儿的便宜
I'm not taking advantage of her.
你的话当真吗
You really believe that?
千真万确
With all my heart.
今天登门拜访的时候
When I knocked on your door today,
我把手枪留在车里了
I left my pistol in my car.
下次再来 我会拿在手上
Next time I come, it will be in my hand.
情况如何 医生
Hey, what's the verdict, Doc?
把他的肺部的积液清除了
Got all the fluid out of his lungs,
但如果动作幅度过大 肺就会再次垮掉
but if he moves around too much, his lung will collapse again,
可能会致命
and it'll probably kill him.
- 确保他别胡来 - 好的 好的
- Make sure he takes it easy. - Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
- 谢谢你的努力 - 不客气
- Thank you for everything you've done. - Appreciate it.
没事的 撑住
You're gonna make it, okay? Just hang in there.
今天狩猎成果颇丰呀
"白人小子"在哪儿
他走了
你说清楚
我撞见他在打猎 遇上了马群 "白人小子"帮我抓
我们说好了
什么意思
如果我让他逃走...
...所有的马都归我
我不信
"白人小子"不会扔下我们
你怎么知道的
他跟你说的吗
白人谎话连篇
他们就这点能耐
托施威你被骗了
他不会忘记自己是俘虏
他骗你教他技能 就为了逃跑
你太信任他了
看着我的眼睛 告诉我
我是科曼切人
我不对同族人说谎
我不想你和树敌
我给你一匹马弥补奴隶的损失
他不是奴隶
圣安东尼奥 红灯区 1915年
"征敌"告诉大家 "白人小子"回去找白人了
你不相信"白人小子"会离开我们吧
我了解他
你也是
人心难测
不是的
你必须去找他
我为什么要这么做
你对他视如己出
我们都看在眼里
即便如此
我的儿子来去自由
你究竟在意什么
你和他不能有接触了 你都快结婚了
什么
你爸爸没告诉你么
没
他接受了"征敌"的礼物
很遗憾
爸爸
"征敌"是不是给你下聘礼了
是啊 你要嫁给他了
你为什么不告诉我
我不想吵架
我不想嫁给他
胡说
我想和别人在一起
你想要的人已经走了
你妈妈和我都很开心
嫁给他 你也会很高兴的
我亲生父亲不会这样逼我
但你亲生父亲却没法保护你
你母亲和我把你放在心上
但我们现在老了 你就得回过头来照顾我们
这是你的责任
快干活
坐吧
别太拘束
你跑不掉的
我想谈一谈
你这么做是不对的
你是你爸爸唯一有价值的东西
就这么跑了 你们家就一无所有了
拜托你放我走
如果取消婚约 我就把马要回来
冬天也不会给你家送肉
你的养父就只好乞求残羹冷炙了
他为你付出这么多
难道你不欠他体面的日子吗
我会当个好丈夫 让你衣食无忧
别犯傻 跟我回去吧
如果我走了 你会来追我吗
不会
永别了 草原之花
等一下
她是自愿回来的吗
是的
谢谢你 女儿 谢谢你